postplanner.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to postplanner.com and Post Planner and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Post Planner include postplanner.com and PP. The PP website is a software as a service site. By using the PP website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, PP may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

  * First and Last Name
  * Mailing Address
  * E-mail Address
  * Phone Number

If you purchase PP's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

If you are a citizen of EU, you can submit a request on our website to delete your data or get a copy of your data and we'll process it right away.

### Use of your Personal Information

PP collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. PP may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from PP and its affiliates.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

PP does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

PP may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. PP may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to PP, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

PP may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on PP or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of PP; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of PP, or the public.

### Tracking User Behavior

PP may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within PP, in order to determine what PP services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within PP to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

### Automatically Collected Information

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by PP. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the PP website.

### Use of Cookies

The PP website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize PP pages, or register with PP site or services, a cookie helps PP to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same PP website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the PP features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the PP services or websites you visit.

### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

### Security of your Personal Information

PP secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. PP uses the following methods for this purpose:

\- SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

### Children Under Thirteen

PP does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

### Disconnecting your PP Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your PP account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR PP ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT (FACEBOOK AND/OR TWITTER), YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED IN THIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting our FAQ.

### E-mail Communications

From time to time, PP may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from PP or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from PP, you may opt out of such communications by Customers may unsubscribe from emails by "replying STOP" or "clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button.

### External Data Storage Sites

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

### California Privacy Rights and Disclosures

California Shine the Light Law. If you are a California resident and we disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes, California’s Shine the Light Law (CA Civil Code Section 1798.83) allows you to request certain information from us about such disclosures. To make a request under the Shine the Light Law, please contact us at privacy@postplanner.com. Please note that under California law, businesses are not required to respond to such requests more than once during any calendar year.

### Changes to this Statement

PP reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

### Contact Information

PP welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that PP has not adhered to this Statement, please contact PP at:

support@postplanner.com

_________________

Effective as of October 1, 2018
